Josh Leckey

Belfast, Northern Ireland, United Kingdom

leckey@yandex.com

07475265165

linkedin.com/in/joshualeckey

Summary

Hello, I am Joshua Leckey, I am a software engineer from Belfast

I'm currently learning Ai Development

All of my projects are available at https://github.com/JoshLeckey

Ask me about Lavavel, Game Development

How to reach me josh@leckey.dev

Know about my experiences https://github.com/JoshLeckey/CV

Experience

Freelance Developer

Freelance (Self employed)

Jun 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

Freelance Developer specializing in web backend, software and automation software for specific tasks.

Loader

HENDERSON WHOLESALE LIMITED

May 2020 - Present (2 years 3 months +)

Education



Queen's University Belfast

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Sep 2020 - Jul 2024

Licenses & Certifications



Programming in C# Certification - Sololearn

26367815-1080



Sololearn - Sololearn

1059-26367815

Skills

.NET Framework • Python (Programming Language) • C# • PHP • Java • JavaScript • Android Development • Node.js • C++ • Android

Honors & Awards

kaines Runner up - Kainos

Jun 2017

Came as a runner up in a coding competition